http://www.vincipro.com/privacy/

Free Shipping on All Purchases. retail orders only. Order Custom Gloves Before 12/3/20 for Delivery by 12/24/20.
Home / Privacy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Vinci collects, uses,
maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a
“User”) of the http://www.vincipro.com website (“Site”). This privacy
policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by
Vinci.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a
variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our
site, place an ordersubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with
other activities, services, features or resources we make available on
our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address,
mailing address, phone number, credit card information,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if
they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse
to supply personally identification information, except that it may
prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users
whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification
information may include the browser name, the type of computer and
technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such
as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and
other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web
browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes
and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set
their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are
being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not
function properly. you may opt-out from receiving targeted
advertisements which may include links to by visiting the NAI website
opt-out page here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or the DAA opt-out page here: http://www.aboutads.info/ or, for end users located in European Territories, the EDAA opt-out page here: http://youronlinechoices.eu/.
How we use collected information
Vinci collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users
as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To process transactionsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when
placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share
this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to
provide the service.To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be
used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It
may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or
questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will
receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product
or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to
unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed
unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact
us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices
and security measures to protect against unauthorized access,
alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information,
username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users
happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and
protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with
PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an
environment as possible for Users.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the
sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors,
licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or
links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the
practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition,
these sites or services, including their content and links, may be
constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy
policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any
other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is
subject to that website\’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Vinci has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When
we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We
encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay
informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we
collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to
review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of
modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms
of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our
Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to
this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of
this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYou must be logged in to post a comment.
Recent Posts
Semi Customized Glove Options
Differences Between Baseball Gloves and Softball Gloves
Best Bat Back Pack Money Can Buy
Search for:
